Provided by SeriousSub
Modify by Blue-Bird™
Long ago, in ancient China,
the Peacocks ruled over Gongmen City.
They brought great joy
and prosperity to the city
for they had invented fireworks.
But their son, Lord Shen,
saw darker power in the fireworks.
What had brought colour and joy
could also bring darkness
and destruction.
Shen's troubled parents
consulted a soothsayer.
She foretold that if Shen
continued down this dark path,
he would be defeated
by a warrior of black and white.
The young lord
set out to change his fate.
But what he did next only sealed it.
Shen returned to his parents
full of pride.
But in their faces, he saw only horror.
He was banished from the city forever.
But Shen swore revenge.
Someday he would return
and all of China would bow at his feet.
It's almost done, Lord Shen,
but we've run out of metal.
Search the farthest villages!
Find more metal!
China will be mine.
And then the Dragon Warrior
joined the Furious Five!
And they became the most
awesomest kung fu team ever!
Enough talk. Let's fight!
- Thirty-three...
- Listen, listen!
You can hear the Dragon Warrior
training right now!
Thirty-three. Stop him!
- Thirty-four.
- It's too dangerous!
- Thirty-five. Stay focused.
- Thirty-six!
- Thirty-seven!
- Yeah!
How is he doing that with his face?
Thirty-eight bean buns!
Yes! New record! You monster!
- Keep going! Hit 40!
- He'll never hit 40.
You guys wait and we'll go to 40.
Do it.
No problem!
Yeah!
Give me a minute.
- He did it!
- Well done, Po!
Your training has paid off.
Master Shifu!
Gotta go. See you later!
You'll save those for me, right?
Flippety-do.
Inner peace.
Master Shifu.
Master Shifu, what do we got?
Pirates? Vandals of Volcano Mountain?
Whatever it is, I will take them down.
'Cause I am in a mood.
I need to get something done,
you know what I mean?
What are you doing?
One of Master Oogway's final teachings.
Awesome!
How did you do that?
- Inner peace.
- Inner piece. That's cool.
- Inner piece of what?
- It is the next phase of your training.
Every master must find his path
to inner peace.
Some choose to meditate for 50 years
in a cave just like this...
...without the slightest taste
of food or water.
Or?
Some find it through
pain and suffering, as I did.
Po, the day you were chosen
as Dragon Warrior
was the worst day of my life.
By far.
Nothing else came close.
It was the worst, most painful,
mind-destroying, horrible moment...
- OK.
- ...I have ever experienced.
But once I realised the problem
was not you, but within me,
I found inner peace and was able
to harness the flow of the universe.
So that's it? I just need inner peace?
My innards are
already super, super peaceful,
so all I need to do
is just get this thing going.
Inner peace, you're going down.
Now show me what you were
doing there with your feet.
I saw you do sort of a fancy foot...
Po! Bandits!
Approaching the Musicians Village.
Danger.
Tell those musicians to start playing
some action music because it is on.
Don't worry, Shifu, I'll master
inner peace as soon as I get back.
No snack stops this time.
Snack stops.
Wait, are you serious?
Get all the metal you can find!
Grab the metal!
Help, help, help, help. Help!
That's everything!
Let's get out of here.
Oh, no.
Wings of Justice!
The Dragon Warrior!
A panda? That's impossible.
My fist hungers for justice.
That was my... fist.
- Get 'em!
- Come on!
Take that!
Po! Incoming!
Thanks, Mantis!
Tigress, Double Death Strike!
Feet of Fury!
Tigress! Monkey!
Viper! Mantis!
Bunny! What?
Oh, sorry.
Help!
- Crane, go!
- I'm on it!
Is everyone OK?
That was awesome!
I got this.
Po!
Chew on that, tubby!
Help.
- Sweetie, are you OK?
- What happened?
I think I saw...
I think...
I gotta go.
Thank you. Thank you for coming
to Dragon Warrior Noodles and Tofu.
- More tea? Lemon sauce?
- No.
If you need anything, just ask.
- Thank you.
- Feet of Fury!
The Dragon Warrior's mop.
He mopped these very floors!
No touching!
You'll get the mop dirty.
- He once waited on me.
- Awesome!
Yeah, I have the stain to prove it.
Hey, where is the Dragon Warrior?
He doesn't work here any more.
He's busy out there
protecting the Valley.
- The Dragon Warrior!
- There he is.
Po!
- Here. OK. Nice kid.
- The Dragon Warrior!
- You should've told me you were coming.
- Hi, Dad.
I would have saved you some stinky tofu.
- Dad, can I talk to you?
- Of course, son.
In honour of my son,
free tofu dessert for everybody!
With purchases.
Oh, it's so good to see you, Po.
Have you lost weight? I can
almost put my wings around you.
Ah, well, maybe a little.
Poor you, you must feel weak.
Let me get you some soup.
No, that's OK, Dad.
I'm not hungry.
Not hungry?
Po, are you all right?
Yeah. No, I'm fine. I just...
Earlier today,
I was fighting these bandits.
Nothing too dangerous.
I mean, they were just, you know...
- Yeah?
- And then the strangest thing happened.
I had this crazy vision.
I think I saw my mom and me,
as a baby.
Mom? A baby?
- Dad?
- What...?
How do I say this?
Where did I come from?
Well, you see, son,
baby geese come from a little egg.
- Don't ask me where the egg comes from.
- Dad, that's not what I meant.
I know it's not.
I think it's time I told you something
I should have told you a long time ago.
OK.
You might have been kind of a...
...adopted.
- I knew it.
- You knew?
- Well, who told you?
- No one. I mean, come on, Dad.
But if you knew,
why didn't you ever say anything?
Why didn't you say anything?
How did I get here, Dad?
Where did I come from?
Actually... you came from this.
It was just another day
at the restaurant.
Time to make the noodles.
I went out to the back, where my
vegetables had just been delivered.
There were cabbages, turnips, radishes.
Only there were no radishes.
Just a very hungry baby panda.
There was no note.
Of course, you could have eaten it.
I waited for someone to come
looking for you, but no one did.
I brought you inside.
Fed you.
Gave you a bath.
And fed you again.
And again.
And tried to put some pants on you.
And then I made a decision
that would change my life forever.
To make my soup without radishes.
And to raise you as my own son.
Xiao Po, my little panda.
And from that moment on,
both my soup and my life
have been that much sweeter.
And, little Po,
that's the end of the story.
Look at me. No, don't look at me.
That's it? That can't be it.
There's gotta be more, Dad!
Well, there was the time
you ate all my bamboo furniture.
It was imported, too.
One dumpling, please,
Dragon Warrior size.
Oh, Po, your story may not
have such a happy beginning,
but look how it turned out.
You got me, you got kung fu,
and you got noodles.
I know. I just have so many questions.
Like how did I ever fit
in this tiny basket?
Why didn't I like pants?
And who am I?
Good. Watch your form.
Good.
Better. Elbow.
Straighten it out!
Shen?
Good afternoon, gentlemen.
Now we've got the pleasantries
out of the way, please leave my house.
- Your house?
- Yes.
Didn't you see the peacock
on the front door?
There you are, Soothsayer.
It seems your fortune-telling skills
are not as good as you thought.
- We shall see, Shen.
- No, you shall see, old goat.
- Where were we?
- What do you want, Shen?
What is rightfully mine. Gongmen City!
Gongmen is under the stewardship
of the Masters' Council,
and we will protect it. Even from you.
I'm so glad you feel that way.
Otherwise, I'd have dragged
that here for nothing.
What's in the box, Shen?
You want to see? It's a gift.
It's your parting gift,
in that it will part you.
Part of you here, part of you there
and part of you way over there,
staining the wall!
You insolent fool!
- Show-off.
- That is a warning.
You are no match for our kung fu.
I agree.
But this is.
Are you familiar
with the master of Gongmen City?
- Master Thundering Rhino?
- Yes.
- Son of legendary Flying Rhino?
And slayer of the Ten Thousand
Serpents in the Valley of Woe?
- He's dead.
- Whoa.
That's impossible.
Rhino's Horn Defence
is impervious to any technique.
It was no technique.
Lord Shen has created a weapon,
one that breathes fire and spits metal.
Unless he is stopped,
this could be the end of kung fu.
- But I just got kung fu!
- And now you must save it.
Go! Destroy this weapon
and bring Lord Shen to justice!
OK, here we go! Here we go!
Wait a second.
How can I do this?
I mean, how can kung fu stop
something that stops kung fu?
Remember, Dragon Warrior,
anything is possible
when you have inner peace.
Inner peace. Inner peace. Inner peace.
Peace on.
- Oh, Po?
- Peace!
Oh, Po, I got you a travel pack.
I packed you food for weeks.
Cookies, buns, vegetables.
And I even packed
all your action figures. See?
I don't know what those are.
Never seen them before in my life.
Dad, you got scratches on my Tigress.
I also packed your paintings
of our best time together,
just in case you get lonely.
That's me and you making noodles.
And that's me and you eating noodles.
And that's me giving you
a piggyback ride.
That cute? On second thought,
I'll hang on to this one.
- Hey, they're waiting for me.
- Of course, of course.
You have a job to do... far from home,
in a strange city, filled with
strange people, and strange noodles,
facing horrible danger
from which you might never return!
- Don't go, Po!
- I gotta go.
I'm the Dragon Warrior.
It's kind of my job to save kung fu.
And if I don't... what am I?
You're my son.
Right?
- Po, it's time.
- Goodbye.
Don't worry, Mr. Ping.
He'll be back before
you can say "noodles".
Noodles.
Come on, guys, let's go!
Yeah!
Yeah...
Yeah, yeah. Yeah...
Mama?
Mom? Dad? Is that you?
Mom! Dad!
Oh, hi. Hey, son. You're back.
Honey, what are you doing here?
But I thought...
We replaced you, dear,
with this lovely radish.
- Radish?
- It's quiet, polite, and, frankly,
does better kung fu.
No. No, no, no.
Wait!
No.
Radish, radish, radish, radish.
Inner pea...
Pea...
Inner peace.
Inner peace! Inner peace! Inner peace!
Inner peace! Inner peace...!
I'm... training.
The mast is not a worthy opponent.
- I am ready.
- OK.
So serious.
I think I prefer the mast.
Apologies. I used to punch the
ironwood trees by the palace to train.
Now I feel nothing.
That's severely cool.
Again!
So, this punching ironwood trees,
how long did you have to do that?
- Twenty years.
- Oh, 20, 20 years.
Is there any, you know, faster way?
You know, until you, you know,
don't feel anything?
No. Besides...
...I don't think
hard style is your thing.
Po, why are you really out here?
I just found out that my dad
isn't really my dad.
Your dad? The goose.
That must have been quite a shock.
Yeah.
- And this bothers you?
- Are you kidding me?
We're warriors, right?
Nerves of steel.
Souls of platinum.
Like you.
So hard-core, you don't feel anything.
- I was...
- So, what are you guys talking about?
Nothing. Nothing.
Po's having daddy issues.
I'm so lucky.
I don't have any problems with my dad.
Maybe it's because Mom
ate his head before I was born.
- I don't know.
- Mantis, this isn't about you.
Po is the one freaking out.
- I'm not freaking out.
- Po.
- I'm freaking in.
- Po!
- What?
- We're here.
Gongmen City.
My father's throne.
He used to let me play here beside him,
promising someday,
this throne would be mine.
A little to the left.
Oh, but it's so heavy, Master!
Thirty years I've waited
for this moment.
Everything must be exactly
how I envisioned it.
And I envisioned it
a little to the left.
Perfect!
With the weapon by my si...
A little bit more.
With the weapon by my side,
all of China will bow before me.
We move out in three days,
when the moon is full
and the tide is high.
Now, you old goat,
why don't you tell me my...
Fortune?
Future. I was going to say future.
Look into your bowl
and tell me what glory awaits.
If you continue on your current path...
...you will find yourself
at the bottom of the stairs.
I see...
I see pain... and anger.
How dare you!
That is the finest silk in the province!
Followed by denial.
This is not fortune-telling.
You're just saying
- what's happening right...
- Now?
The most important time is now.
But if you really want
to see the future...
Oh, what do you see?
A peacock...
...is defeated by a warrior
of black and white.
Nothing has changed.
That's impossible, and you know it.
It is not impossible, and he knows it.
Who?
- Lord Shen! I saw a panda!
- A panda?
A kung fu warrior.
It fought like a demon!
Big and furry.
Soft and squishy.
Kind of plush and cuddly.
There are no more pandas.
Even with his poor eyesight,
he can see the truth.
Why is it that you cannot?
Find this panda and bring him to me!
Yes, sir!
One panda lives.
That does not make you right.
You're right.
Being right makes me right.
Then I will kill him and make you wrong.
Will you stop that!
That must be Shen's palace
on the other side of the city.
Great. We'll march into the tower
and proclaim,
"We are the Dragon Warrior
and the Furious Five,
and we are here
to bring you to justice!"
What are you doing?
This place is crawling with wolves.
Hey, isn't that the guy
who hammered you in the face?
I do not like that guy.
We need to get to that tower
without being spotted by those wolves.
Got it. Stealth mode.
- Get out of the way!
- Foiled again.
Now, where'd those noodles go?
Hello. I couldn't help but...
Yeah, OK. Anyway, where was I?
- Where's Po?
- How can we lose a guy that big?
OK.
Guys! Guys?
- Hey, Po.
- What? Sorry.
So that was stealth mode, huh?
To be honest,
not one of my stronger modes.
...gold in there, come on!
This rice is raw!
You stole all my metal pots
for Lord Shen!
Either you cook my rice, or I cook you!
- My apologies, but...
- Po, do something.
How am I supposed to help her cook rice
without getting caught?
- Wait, I have a better idea.
- ...two...
...one.
- Hey.
We're here to liberate the city
and bring Shen to justice.
- You will need help.
- Thank you, brave sheep,
but it's too dangerous. I can't let you.
Oh, no, not me.
It's not safe to speak here.
Right.
I'm talking about Masters Ox and Croc.
They're in Gongmen Jail
on Black Dragon Alley.
What? They're still alive?
They must be in that jail
gathering intelligence,
hatching a plot to use their
awesomeness to defeat the weapon!
OK, let's go!
- Thanks, sheep.
- Hey! Stop that costume!
- Hold it right there!
- Get them!
- Sorry!
Take that!
- Keep going!
- Faster!
Hey, stop!
- Look out! Watch it!
- Sorry!
Surround him.
Now!
Gotcha!
What? Where'd he go?
- Spread out! Search everywhere!
- What about over there?
- Is "there" a part of "everywhere"?
- I... I guess.
Then search there!
They must be close. I can feel
a kung fu chill riding up my spine.
Sorry, Po. It's just me.
Look. Gongmen Jail.
Aw, it's cute.
Cute, huh?
Nice work, Po.
At the first sign of trouble,
I'll give you a signal.
- You mean like Crane does?
- Yeah.
Excuse me,
when have I ever made that noise?
Master Ox! Master!
The ferocious Master Croc!
And Master Storming Ox.
I can't believe we're rescuing
actual legends of kung fu.
We're gonna free you from those
bonds of injustice. No problem.
Gotta be a key around here. No,
they wouldn't leave a key around here.
Oh, good! You found it.
Come on, you guys! Yeah!
We're coming for you, Shen!
Guys, are we going or not?
Do you want to meet us there later?
I mean, you do want to
take back your city, right?
Of course we do.
But if we stand up to Shen,
he will turn the weapon on the city.
Listen to yourself.
You're protecting Gongmen City
by not protecting Gongmen City?
- If we all fight together...
- Then the weapon would kill everyone.
Oh, would it?
Then we use... a sneak attack!
- We get inside and then...
- And then you will be stopped...
...by the unstoppable weapon.
Nothing's unstoppable except for me
when I'm stopping you
from telling me something's unstoppable!
Master Ox,
I'm not letting you stay in this cell.
I'd like to see you get me out!
You guys see that?
It's called being awesome.
Come on! Whatever
happened to being heroes?
The only hero in this town
is a dead one!
Like I said, you are not
getting me out of this cell!
Yes!
All right, let's go!
I get the top bunk.
It's time to surrender, panda.
Kung fu is dead.
I...
You...
Kung fu is dead? Fine!
You stay in your prison of fear
with bars made of hopelessness.
And all you get are three
square meals a day of shame!
With despair for dessert.
We'll take on Shen and prove
to all those who are hungry
for justice and honour
that kung fu still lives!
Yeah!
Monkey?!
You! You're mine!
I'll tell you what's gonna be yours!
My fist in your plush, cuddly,
super-soft face!
Get him!
- Get me out of here!
- Yes, sir!
Stop him!
Faster!
Yeah! Go, go!
- Lose him!
- Yes, sir!
- Viper!
- Hang on!
- What?
- Watch out!
Uncool! Very uncool!
Try this!
Guys, guys, guys!
Maybe something smaller!
No, no! Oh, no, no.
Cute bunnies, off the face.
Excuse me! OK, pardon me!
Fire!
We've lost them.
Again! Again!
Crane, catch!
Gotcha!
Guys, guys, guys, guys,
give me a shove!
Mantis, now!
Is that all you got? It feels like
I'm fighting a big old fluffy cloud!
Well, this cloud is about
to bring the thunder!
Your turn!
Why... are... there...
so... many... signs?!
Come here! Alaka-squasho!
Yes! Taste the defeat!
Let me tell you something.
Next time you mess with a panda,
you better bring a whole a...
Guess nobody told you,
if you mess with the wolf,
you get the fangs.
I've hit you twice.
What are you going to do now?
We surrender!
You can chain my body, but you will
never chain my... warrior spirit.
- Hey, don't forget the little guy.
- Did you just call...?
- Po, what are you doing?
- Trust me. I got a pl...
No way. Eight-point acupressure cuffs?
Just like the ones that held Tai Lung.
The more you move, the tighter they get.
These are the best cuffs!
Greetings, panda. At last we meet!
No, no, no...
We meet at last! Yes, that's it.
Greetings, panda. We meet at...
- You are afraid for a reason.
- I am not afraid.
He is coming to me in chains.
- If anyone should be afraid, it's...
- You.
Don't even think about it.
I hope this turns out better than
your plan to cook rice in your stomach
by eating it raw
and then drinking boiling water.
This plan's nothing like that plan.
- How?
- 'Cause this one's going to work.
Keep moving.
Ah, my old enemy...
...stairs.
Thanks for carrying me
those last few flights. OK.
I threw up a little bit
on the third floor.
Someone might want to clean that up.
Is there some sort of evil janitor
or something?
Greetings, panda.
- We meet at...
- Hey, how you doing?
Hey.
You've grown up bigger than I thought.
Hey... enough with the poking around.
Strong. Healthy.
Look, I don't know who you are,
but please stand aside, sir.
- That's a lady.
- Oh! Sorry.
The beard threw me.
It's kind of misleading.
- False advertising.
- Enough of this nonsense!
Bring the prisoners to me.
Sorry, ma'am. Get ready, guys.
Keep your eyes peeled for the...
weapon!
Sparrow kick!
We did it! I just kung fu-ed it!
Did you guys see that? I was all like...
Do you actually believe this is
the warrior destined to defeat me?
I do not. I know he is.
Oh, look at him.
A lifetime to plot his revenge
- and he comes to me on his knees.
- What? A lifetime?
I did not have a lifetime.
We only heard about Master Rhino
a few days ago,
- and we came to avenge him!
- You've come to avenge nothing else?
Well, yeah.
All the pots and pans that you stole.
- I'm gonna want those back.
- Nothing else?
You probably did some other evil stuff
along the way. I don't know.
- What else did you do?
- You don't know?
Know what? What's so funny?
The very thing
that you clearly do not know!
OK, enough of these riddles!
Would you guys spill the beans?
First, we come in and the weapon
is tiny. Surprise, it's big.
And then the lady over here,
I think it's a guy, 'cause he's got...
The only reason you are still alive
is that I find your stupidity
mildly amusing.
Well, thank you. But I find your
evilness extremely annoying.
Who do you think you are, panda?
Who do you think I am, peacock?
Why are we laughing?
Take aim.
Fire.
Well, light the... thing!
I did!
Fear the bug!
Get the weapon!
Tigress!
You... You were there.
Yes. Yes, I was.
- You just let Shen get away!
- At least we destroyed the weapon.
Fire!
Oh. No, he's got way more.
- My wing!
- Help, Po!
Coming!
- Watch out!
- Po!
- Help me up!
- No. Get him down.
Use the ropes.
Run, run, little panda!
- Po, come on. We need you to focus!
- I got it, I got it!
Bring it down!
- We're trapped!
- This way!
Goodbye!
Fire!
Get back!
The only way out is up.
What?
Follow me! Come on!
Where are they going?
- To the top!
- Come on! Keep going!
Here we go!
- You idiot!
- My nose!
Call in the wolves! All of them!
I want them ready to move!
The Year of the Peacock begins now!
Right now?
'Cause it's the middle of the year,
so you'd only get like
a half of the Year of the Peacock.
And this is the Year, of course,
of the Peacock.
Happy New Year, sir.
Get the wolves ready.
We're loading the ships now.
Now!
Now, now, now, now, now!
Move! Move, move, move, move!
This way.
Let's go.
Oh, you! What did you do?
It's chaos up there.
What happened to stopping Shen?
Yeah.
Guys, come on.
Give me a little credit.
I meant for him to get away.
'Cause... it was a trick. It was a plot.
I was thinking...
I'll figure out his plot more.
That makes no sense.
What do you mean? Sure it does.
Po, the truth.
You had Shen. What happened?
What are you talking about?
I don't know what you're talking about.
I... Yeah...
OK, he caught me off guard.
The truth.
Fine. They will keep you
far from danger.
- Real far.
- What?
You're staying here.
Wait! I have to go ba...
You're staying here!
I'm going. And you can't stop me.
OK. I wasn't ready that time.
Guys? Don't.
Ready.
Look!
Stay down.
- I have to get to him.
- Then tell me why!
He was there! OK?
The peacock was there
the last time I saw my parents.
He knows what happened.
Where I came from.
Who I am.
Look, I'm going.
I have to know.
The hard core can't understand.
Tigress, no!
The hard core do understand.
But I can't watch my friend be killed.
- We're going.
- Maybe you can't watch me be killed?
- Stop being a wimp.
- And she's back.
- No.
- Don't worry, kid.
You're better off here.
You were wrong, Soothsayer.
We sail to victory tonight.
Your magic panda is clearly a fool.
Are you certain it is the panda
who is a fool?
You just destroyed
your ancestral home, Shen.
A trivial sacrifice...
when all of China is my reward.
Then will you finally be satisfied?
Will the subjugation of the whole world
finally make you feel better?
It's a start. I might also convert
the basement into a dungeon.
The cup you choose to fill
has no bottom.
It is time to stop this madness.
Why on earth would I do that?
So your parents can rest in peace.
My parents hated me.
Do you understand?
They wronged me...
and I will make it right.
They loved you.
They loved you so much that
having to send you away killed them.
The dead exist in the past...
and I must tend to the future.
Set the soothsayer free.
She's no use to me.
Goodbye, Shen.
I wish you happiness.
Happiness must be taken.
And I will take mine.
- Hurry it up!
- Move it!
If all of those weapons
leave the building, China will fall.
- We bring down the building.
- Hey, guys. How about this?
- This will work!
- All right, let's go.
I can't feel my face.
Did you hear him call it
Year of the Peacock?
- Hey.
OK. So, keep it cool.
Keep it cool. Keep it cool.
You! Where are you going?
On your feet! And wipe those
stupid grins off your faces.
Move, you dogs!
Faster, faster! Load them all!
Greetings, panda.
- Tell me what happened that night.
- What night?
- That night.
- Ah, that night.
Yes! We're talking
about the same night, right?
Yes, I was there. Yes. I watched
as your parents abandoned you.
It's a terrible thing.
I believe it went something like this.
Here's your New Year's gift.
Hope you like it,
'cause you can't return it.
Po? What's he doing here?
Return it! Return it!
Are you willing to die
to find the truth?
You bet I am.
Although I'd prefer not to.
We got them. Go!
You looking for me?
I said that too soon, didn't I?
Po!
Po, get away from him.
I'll get up. Here we go.
- No more running, Shen.
- So it seems.
Now... answers.
Oh, you want to know so badly.
You think knowing will heal you, huh?
Fill some crater in your soul?
Well, here's your answer.
Your parents didn't love you.
But here...
...let me heal you!
No!
Yeah, like you could make me drink that.
If I wanted you dead,
I would have left you in that river.
- Well, why save me?
- So you can fulfill your destiny.
What are you talking about?
Where am I?
What is this place?
I'm surprised you remember so little.
But you were so little when it happened.
Perhaps you do remember.
What? It's just a stupid nightmare.
Nightmare? Or memory?
This was a thriving village.
Young Shen was in line
to rule Gongmen City.
But he wanted more.
I foretold that someone would stand
in his way. A panda.
But I never could have foretold
what came next.
Get them all!
Take our son and run away! Go!
Stop fighting. Let it flow.
Your story may not have
such a happy beginning,
but that doesn't
make you who you are.
It is the rest of your story.
Who you choose to be.
So, who are you, panda?
I am Po.
And I'm gonna need a hat.
Such sad, sad faces.
But now is a time only for joy.
You are going to be part
of something beautiful.
Once we reach the harbour,
in front of all the world,
you and your precious kung fu will die.
Then China will know to bow before me.
Set sail!
What is that?
Honestly, guys,
I never thought I'd die like this.
I always thought I'd meet
a nice girl and settle down and...
...then she'd eat my head.
- So sad.
- We cannot give up hope.
Po would want us to remain strong.
Hard-core. Right, Tigress?
- Lord Shen, what about the bridge?
- Nothing stands in my way.
Fire!
You coward!
Po?
How many times do I have to kill
the same stinking panda?
Shen!
A panda stands between you
and your destiny.
What?
Prepare yourself for a
hot serving of justice.
Your reign of terror comes to an end.
- What?
- And now, free the Five!
Disc of Destruction!
OK. Take aim!
Ready?
You can't follow me.
Just get him!
- Yeah. Here we go.
- Come on!
- No, no, no, don't shoot!
- Don't shoot!
No, don't shoot!
- You don't shoot!
- I won't shoot if you won't shoot.
Yeah!
- Don't shoot! Cross fire!
- Attack!
- Catch of Freedom!
- Monkey!
Impressive, Dragon Warrior.
What's your plan?
- Step one, free the Five.
- What's step two?
Honestly, I didn't think
I'd make it this far.
Po!
Stop Shen before he gets to the harbour.
Nice!
Viper, Puppet of Death!
Tigress!
- Master Ox!
- Jump!
- And Croc!
- Vengeance is served.
- Why did you...?
- Your friend there is very persuasive.
Master Shifu!
Quickly. Use their boats
to block the way.
Crane!
Wings of Justice!
Yeah!
What?
I love you guys.
Why aren't we firing?
They're taking out our gunners, sir.
They're getting close.
Fire! Fire at them!
- But, sir, we'll kill our own.
- I said fire at them!
Fire!
No.
Po!
Tigress?
As you wish.
Let's finish this.
Fire!
Inner peace.
Again!
Yeah!
Kill him! Somebody kill him!
What? No. No!
Keep firing! Keep firing!
Skadoosh.
How did you...?
How did you do it?
You know, you just keep your elbows up
and keep the shoulders loose.
Not that. How did you find peace?
I took away your parents. Everything.
I scarred you for life.
See, that's the thing, Shen.
Scars heal.
No, they don't. Wounds heal.
Oh, yeah. What do scars do?
They fade, I guess?
- I don't care what scars do.
- You should, Shen.
You gotta let go of that stuff from
the past, 'cause it just doesn't matter.
The only thing that matters
is what you choose to be now.
You're right.
Then I choose... this!
That was pretty hard-core.
- Po!
- You did it!
- Come here! Yeah!
- Don't ever do that again, please.
It seems you have found inner peace.
And at such a young age.
Well, I had a pretty good teacher.
What do you mean he's not here?
It's my son's birthday.
All he wanted was to meet
the Dragon Warrior.
How about some tofu birthday cake
instead, huh?
You know, I think we'll
just try again another time.
When do you think he'll be back?
I don't know. OK, I don't know.
Maybe never.
I mean, I worry, OK?
But that's my job, I'm his dad.
At least, I was his dad.
Why did he have to go and save China?
I know why.
But why? He's just one little panda.
So, how did it go?
Did you save China?
Yep.
Well, I knew you would.
That's why I had new signs made.
"My son saved China.
You, too, can save.
Buy one dumpling, get one free."
Hey, that's a pretty good deal.
- Would you like to try one?
- Maybe later.
There's something I should tell you.
While I was gone,
I found the village where I was born.
I found out how I ended up
in that radish basket.
You did?
- I know who I am.
- You do?
I'm your son.
I love you, Dad.
I love you, too, son.
Delicious, fat radishes!
You're probably hungry.
Let me make you something to eat.
What are you talking about? I'll cook.
- No, no, I'll cook.
- Dad!
Well, it's the least I can do.
You saved China.
No, it's the least I can do.
You raised me.
- Po.
- Dad.
- Po!
- OK.
Let's both cook. Together.
Together.
No, I'll cook.
My son is alive.
Provided by SeriousSub
Modify by Blue-Bird™